<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Designing Writing</title>
    <link>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Designing Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 17:41:29 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Hugo</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/post/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 17:41:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/post/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;d like to install Hugo and work with it on your own, and contribute to the webtext in that way, here are the links to the different tools and repositories that I am using:
 Hugo GitHub Repository Atom GitHub Desktop  I will gladly work with anyone on working through how to use the tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Submission Guide</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/page/submission-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:56:51 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/page/submission-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hey all, to help streamline the process of submitting materials for me to upload, here are a few guideline that will be helpful. First, please format your pieces as Plain Text, as this will strip random formatting from the document. You can do this out of Word by doing a save as, plain text, or out of Google Docs as a Download As Plain Text. I will help with some of that workflow as we go through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown Guide</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 May 2018 22:56:38 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/designing-writing/page/markdown-cheat-sheet/</guid>
      <description>Here is a guide to markdown, taken from the GoHugo docs. As mentioned in the submission guide, you can also use a number of online markdown editors such as stackedit.io, Dillinger. I use a program called Atom, which is very much a programming text editor.
This cheat sheet is set up for common usage scenarios for our text. I will provide links for futher information. As always, I am always availble to help, just send an email.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>